<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bitotsav \'19</string>

    <!--Images Content Descriptions-->
    <string name="desc_subscribe">Subscribe to alerts</string>
    <string name="desc_event_description">Hide or show description</string>
    <string name="desc_share_feed_message">Share</string>
    <string name="desc_bit_logo">BIT Mesra</string>
    <string name="event_details_short">%s • %s</string>

    <!-- Home -->
    <string name="schedule_title">Schedule</string>
    <string name="info_title">Info</string>
    <string name="feed_title">Updates</string>
    <string name="profile_title">Profile</string>

    <!-- Schedule -->
    <string name="filters_label_sheet_title">Filters</string>
    <string name="filters_label_clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="filters_label_starred">Starred Only</string>

    <!-- Login -->
    <string name="login_label_email">Email</string>
    <string name="login_label_password">Password</string>
    <!-- TODO [Refactor]: Could this be 'Begin' ? -->
    <string name="login_label_login">Login</string>
    <string name="login_label_register">Register</string>

    <!-- Registration -->
    <string name="registration_title">Registration</string>

    <!-- Step 1 -->
    <string name="registration_label_name">Name</string>
    <string name="registration_label_phone">
        Phone No <small><small>(For First OTP)</small></small>
    </string>
    <string name="registration_label_email">
        Email <small><small>(For Second OTP)</small></small>
    </string>
    <string name="registration_label_password">Password</string>
    <string name="registration_label_next_step_one">Get OTPs</string>

    <!-- Step 2 -->
    <string name="registration_label_phoneOtp">Phone OTP</string>
    <string name="registration_label_emailOtp">Email OTP</string>
    <string name="registration_label_next_step_two">Verify OTPs</string>

    <!-- Step 3 -->
    <string name="registration_label_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="registration_label_college">College</string>
    <string name="registration_label_year">Year</string>
    <string name="registration_label_rollNo">Roll No</string>
    <string name="registration_label_source">Source</string>
    <!-- TODO [Refactor]: Should this be 'Get Bitotsav ID' ? -->
    <string name="registration_label_next_step_three">Let\'s Rock !!</string>

    <!-- Event Detail -->
    <string name="event_label_description">Description</string>
    <string name="event_label_rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="event_label_status">Status</string>
    <string name="event_label_time">Time</string>
    <string name="event_label_venue">Venue</string>
    <string name="event_label_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="event_label_result">Result</string>
    <string name="event_label_category">Category</string>
    <string name="event_label_team_size">Team Size</string>
    <string name="event_label_prizes">Up For Grabs</string>
    <string name="event_label_rank1">1</string>
    <string name="event_label_rank2">2</string>
    <string name="event_label_rank3">3</string>
    <string name="event_placeholder_tba">TBA</string>
    <string name="event_placeholder_tba_long">To Be Announced</string>
    <string name="event_placeholder_no_coordinators">Contact events team.</string>
    <string name="event_format_time">%1$s (Day %2$d)</string>
    <string name="event_format_time_venue">%1$s • %2$s</string>
    <string name="event_format_team_size">%1$d - %2$d</string>
    <string name="event_format_prize">%,d Cash Prize</string>
    <string name="event_format_points">%,d Championship Points</string>
    <string name="event_format_leader_name">%s\'s Team</string>
    <string name="event_format_share_title">Share %s with</string>
    <string name="event_format_share_text">
        Have you heard about %1$s ? Check it out! #Bitotsav19 #ColorsOfAsia\n%2$s
    </string>
    <string name="event_label_register">Register</string>
    <string name="event_label_deregister">Deregister</string>
    <string name="event_format_registration_message">See you at %s !!</string>
    <string name="event_format_deregistration_message">Abandoned %s 😢</string>

    <!-- Team Registration -->
    <string name="team_registration_label_format_title">%s Registration</string>
    <string name="team_registration_label_format_email">Member %d Email</string>
    <string name="team_registration_label_format_bitotsav_id">
        Member %d Bitotsav Id (BT19/*****)
    </string>
    <string name="event_team_registration_label_member_count">Select Member Count</string>
    <string name="event_team_registration_label_register">Register</string>
    <string name="championship_team_registration_label_team_name">Team Name</string>
    <string name="championship_team_registration_label_register">Register</string>

    <!-- Profile -->
    <string name="profile_label_format_title">Hi %s !!</string>
    <string name="profile_label_bitotsav_credentials">Your Bitotsav Details</string>
    <string name="profile_label_bitotsav_id">Bitotsav ID</string>
    <string name="profile_label_email">Registered Email</string>
    <string name="profile_label_register">Register for Championship</string>
    <string name="profile_label_championship_team">Championship Team</string>
    <string name="profile_label_championship_score">Championship Score</string>
    <string name="profile_label_registrations">Registrations</string>
    <string name="profile_label_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="profile_format_registration_message">
        Welcome to the Championship, %s!!
    </string>

    <!-- Feed -->
    <string name="feed_format_share_title">Share %s</string>
    <string name="feed_format_share_text">%s \n#Bitotsav19 #ColorsOfAsia</string>

    <!-- Info -->
    <string name="info_title_bitotsav_bit">Bitotsav</string>
    <string name="info_title_contact">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="info_title_about_app">About App</string>

    <!-- Bitotsav -->
    <string name="info_bitotsav_bitotsav_19_label">Bitotsav 19</string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_bitotsav_19_content">
        Deemed as an institute of national importance, Birla Institute of Technology, Mesra,
        is one of the country\'s most honourable and distinguished educational university.
        It was founded and established by the visionary industrialist, B.M. Birla over more
        than six decades ago, and has been creating waves of success ever since. The massive
        850 acre campus has been home to diverse cultures, multitudinous talent, and
        inspiring leaders.\n\n

        BIT Mesra has not only produced some of the finest technocrats in the country, but
        has also churned out winners in professions as diverse as music, art, and
        literature. Our annual cultural extravaganza, BITOTSAV, is an affluent celebration
        of the rich cultural heritage that resides in our country, and an attempt to revel
        in the euphoric essence of India\'s cultural potency. BITOTSAV has a plethora of
        events to realize its cause of bringing students from all spheres and from all
        places, together, to enjoy culture while supporting something of societal
        importance. As the grandeur of BITOTSAV keeps on growing, this year\'s BITOTSAV is
        set to be majestic: bigger and better than ever before. With enthralling events,
        mesmerizing nights, enticing performances by prominent celebrities and a whole lot
        of dance and music, we welcome you to BITOTSAV19.
    </string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_theme_label">Theme: Colours Of Asia</string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_theme_content">
        “We are, at almost every point of our day, immersed in cultural diversity: faces,
        clothes, smells, attitudes, values, traditions, behaviours, beliefs, rituals.”

        <annotation alignment="end">
            \n- Randa Abdel-Fattah
        </annotation>\n\n

        From the ‘Khokhloma’ painting symbolizing the high importance of forests and nature in
        Russian culture and its history; to ‘Liwa’ the traditional dance performed in
        Eastern Arabia; from the traditional Chinese ‘Qipao’ dress, to over 720 dialects and
        22 official languages in India; form ‘yakuniku’ a Japanese style of cooking, to
        ‘Teochew opera’ in Singapore; a deep vein of history courses through all the
        countries of Asia. Culture has ever since been the lifeblood of any vibrant society
        to tell their stories, celebrate, remember the past, entertain and envisage the
        future. The variant forms of art, architecture and language, folk music,
        invigorating dance and eclectic cuisines, marks off even various regions in a
        country characterizing their inherent traditional origin through different
        civilizations. Melding of culture and traditions through globalisation and
        technological advances have increased their historically grounded and validated
        contributions and brought about much needed futuristic changes. Through the theme
        “Celebration of Cultures-Colours of Asia” BITOTSAV’19 procures to contribute in its
        own distinctive way to celebrate the rich, large, complex and variegated cultures of
        humanity.
    </string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_social_cause_label">Social Cause: विशेष</string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_social_cause_content">
        Pertaining from birth or caused through unavoidable circumstances or accident,
        disability has always been considered as a character to endow compassion, pity and
        empathy. While throughout the world many changes have taken place in status and
        treatment of persons with disabilities, the remnants of tradition and past belief
        influence present-day practices affecting such groups. Even today, our country has
        about 30 million handicaps, out of which 50% are uneducated. In a society embracing
        illiteracy and apartheid on grounds of one’s physical disabilities, the situations
        of the incapacitated are still in dire straits. Discriminative attitude can
        stigmatize persons with disabilities, imposing artificial limitations upon them,
        denying them equal opportunities for development and living, and inequitably
        demoting them to second-class citizens to be pitied.\n\n

        Started back in 1960, the Disability Rights Movement has thrived to bring forth a change in
        the world by breaking institutional, physical and societal barriers that had been
        preventing people with disabilities from living their lives like other citizens.
        This BITOTSAV we pledge to part take in and contribute our bit to secure equal
        opportunities and equal rights for all people with disabilities.
    </string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_social_campaign_label">Social Campaign: Lost In Echoes</string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_social_campaign_content">
        If we trace the trails of time, we come across various art forms, be it music, dance
        or the fine arts, which have, over time, lost their sheen and significance. But
        their grandeur and pageantry are unparalleled. India has, since time immemorial,
        been a country which has boasted of unity in diversity and the multifarious nature
        of our country is exhibited in its rich cultural heritage. But due to modernisation,
        this vibrant culture is getting lost. From the Madhubani painting of Bihar to he
        Toda embroidery of the Nilgiri hills, these art forms, which show us our glorious
        past are gradually attriting and it is about time that we do something about it. In
        an effort to revive the the magnificence of our rich culture, we at BITOTSAV\'19 have
        pledged to bring to the fore, such art forms via various awareness campaigns,
        workshops and talks.
    </string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_online_campaign_label">
        Online Campaign: Responsible Netizenship
    </string>
    <string name="info_bitotsav_online_campaign_content">
        To acquaint one and all with this term, a Netizen is a general word that is used for
        any person that uses the internet. A responsible Netizen is one who abides by the
        rules of the online world. Of course, the internet is not restricted to a set of
        rules and regulations, and is subject to use as and how desired by the end
        consumer. This is where the concept of responsible Netizenship kicks in. A
        responsible netizen, is a person who has a moral approach towards the usage of the
        internet: one who respects the online community, and abides by the so called
        \'Netiquettes\'.\n\n

        To spread awareness regarding the same, this year\'s social campaign for BITOTSAV is
        chosen as Responsible Netizenship. As the usage of internet increases manifold, it
        becomes imperative to ensure that people use it with a certain sense of
        responsibility. The entire BITOTSAV\'19 team will strive to ensure that people learn
        about the duties and responsibilities of a netizen, and urge others to do the same.
        As the usage of the internet is increasing manifold, it is very imperative to be
        responsible whilst using it. The entire BITOTSAV\'19 team will strive to ensure that
        people learn about the duties and responsibilities of a netizen, and urge others to
        do the same.
    </string>

    <!-- Contact -->
    <string name="info_contact_label_faculty">Faculty Coordinators</string>
    <string name="info_contact_label_student">Student Coordinators</string>
    <string name="info_contact_faculty1_name">Dr. Kirti Avishek</string>
    <string name="info_contact_faculty1_contact">kavishek@bitmesra.ac.in</string>
    <string name="info_contact_faculty2_name">Dr. Mrinal Pathak</string>
    <string name="info_contact_faculty2_contact">mrinalpathak@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="info_contact_student1_name">Gyan Vardhan</string>
    <string name="info_contact_student1_contact">+91 7903002489</string>
    <string name="info_contact_student2_name">Aakrati Jain</string>
    <string name="info_contact_student2_contact">+91 9425797926</string>
    <string name="info_contact_location_uri">https://maps.app.goo.gl/354f8</string>
    <string name="info_contact_email_uri">mailto:bitotsav@bitmesra.ac.in</string>
    <string name="info_contact_website_uri">https://bitotsav.in</string>
    <string name="info_contact_facebook_uri">https://facebook.com/bitotsav</string>
    <string name="info_contact_instagram_uri">https://instagram.com/bitotsav_19</string>

</resources>
